You can change the boundary to works, agent, concept or all.
Since we have not yet started working with works as our own entities
If you do not get many hits when you search for works.
As a default, the search is also set to free text.
You can then define further here by selecting ISBN, ISSN or Main title.
If you delineate to ISBN, you can search for ISBN with or without a hyphen.
If you search for ISBN as a free text, search without a hyphen.
You can also click Search in the main menu.
Then you come to a view where you can search in Libris or other sources.
It is important to always seek carefully in Libris first to be sure that you do not create duplicates.
If you do not find what you are looking for in Libris, you can move on to other sources.
Here you can search other databases and import an entry.